About
rwjlai is a website showcasing cards created by Ruth for her additional piece. Zimu was responsible for all design and implementation of the site. This involved coding, from scratch, the site in HTML and CSS, adapting pre-existing javascript code to meet the site’s needs, and uploading and hosting the site on the World Wide Web for all to see. 
Thanks to Lokesh Dhakar, author of <a href=”http://lokeshdhakar.com/projects/lightbox2/”>Lightbox</a>, the image viewer I adapted for this site.


Student IDs:
	Ruth Lai (????????)
	Zimu Zhang (26081628)

Click here to expand my rationale
